https://mangetout.ae/privacy-policy

Login
Forgot your password?
Sign in with.
New Customer?
Create An Account
Search:
array(4) {
["width_config"] => string(0) ""
["header-top"] => array(2) {
[0] => array(2) {
["child_blocks"] => array(1) {
[0] => string(64) "{"type":"static_block","title":"Call Us","identifier":"call_us"}"
}
["custom_class"] => string(71) "border-dash col-lg-6 col-xs-12 col-md-6 col-sm-6 no-padding ui-sortable"
}
[1] => array(2) {
["child_blocks"] => array(1) {
[0] => string(78) "{"type":"custom","id":"2","title":"Top Links","group_id":"1","store_view":"0"}"
}
["custom_class"] => string(71) "border-dash col-lg-6 col-xs-12 col-md-6 col-sm-6 no-padding ui-sortable"
["child_blocks"] => array(1) {
[0] => string(78) "{"type":"custom","id":"4","title":"Site Logo","group_id":"1","store_view":"0"}"
}
["custom_class"] => string(62) "border-dash col-lg-4 col-xs-12 col-sm-4 no-padding ui-sortable"
}
[1] => array(2) {
["child_blocks"] => array(4) {
[0] => string(94) "{"type":"custom","id":"3","title":"Store Language (dropdown)","group_id":"1","store_view":"0"}"
[1] => string(84) "{"type":"custom","id":"11","title":"Store Currency","group_id":"1","store_view":"0"}"
[2] => string(94) "{"type":"custom","id":"12","title":"customer_form_mini_login","group_id":"1","store_view":"0"}"
[3] => string(80) "{"type":"custom","id":"5","title":"Search X Bar","group_id":"","store_view":"0"}"
}
["custom_class"] => string(72) "border-dash col-lg-8 col-xs-12 col-sm-8 main-menu no-padding ui-sortable"
["child_blocks"] => array(1) {
[0] => string(58) "{"type":"static_block","title":"menu","identifier":"menu"}"
}
["custom_class"] => string(61) "border-dash col-lg-9 col-md-9 main_nav no-padding ui-sortable"
}
[1] => array(2) {
["child_blocks"] => array(1) {
[0] => string(84) "{"type":"custom","id":"7","title":"Dropdown Cart 1","group_id":"1","store_view":"0"}"
}
["custom_class"] => string(64) "border-dash col-lg-3 col-md-3 right_nav_h no-padding ui-sortable"
}
}
}
MenuHome Gift by occasionOccasionsBirthdayNew BabyWedding & AnniversaryLove & RomanceGet Well SoonThank YouCongratulationsView All >>Occasions to ComeChristmasChinese New YearValentinesMother's DayEasterFather's DayRamadan & EidYear End Teachers GiftsEid Al AdhaBreast Cancer AwarenessDiwaliHalloweenUAE National Day CategoriesCakes & CupcakesOrganic RangeThe Luxury CollectionGift HampersFruit BasketsChocolate TreatsArabic & Asian DelightsBath & BeautyCheese HampersFor KidsCare PackagesBalloonsPicnic HampersSoft ToysFor HerFor HimPerfumeBoxes, Baskets & PackagingPersonalised GiftsSizzling ExperiencesView All >>Cakes FlowersView All >>PlantsMixed BouquetBasket ArrangementsPlatinum CollectionRosesLiliesTulipsCarnationsOrchidsCorporate ContractsSympathyDealsCorporateContact
0
AED 0.00
Your shopping cart is empty!
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy describes the ways in which we collect, store, use and protect your personal information and it is important for you to review this privacy policy.
By "personal information" we mean information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person.
By providing us with your personal information you expressly consent to us processing your personal information in accordance with the terms of our privacy policy.
We may amend our privacy policy at any time by posting a revised version on the website
The revised version will be effective at the time we post it and, following such posting, your continued use of the Site will constitute your express consent to us continuing to process your personal information in accordance with the terms of our revised privacy policy.
Collection of Personal Information
We collect personal information that you provide us, such as when you
Sign up for or register on www.mangetout.ae
Register to use www.mangetout.ae or sign up for newsletters and/or notification of special promotions on www.mangetout.ae
Place an order or purchase products or services at our online store or on the telephone
Contact us for any reason by telephone through Customer Services
Use of Personal Information
We only use your personal information to provide services and customer support to you,  to measure and improve our services to you, to prevent illegal activities troubleshoot problems, collect fees, provide you with promotional emails and verify information you give us with third parties. For example, we may share some of the personal information you give us with banks or credit card authorisation, processing and verification services or with third parties for fraud screening purposes.
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose your personal information to law enforcement agencies, government agencies or other third parties where we are compelled so to do by court order or similar legal procedure; where we are required to disclose your personal information to comply with the law; where we are co-operating with an ongoing law enforcement investigation or where we have a good faith belief that our disclosure of your personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss.
By registering on the Site, you give us your express consent to receive promotional emails about our services and emails announcing changes to, and new features on the website. If, at any time, you decide that you do not wish to receive any such emails, you can opt out of receiving such emails by clicking on the link at the bottom of any of the emails or by going to the My Account section of the website.
We do not retain debit card PINs or credit card security codes, Furthermore, when you enter personal information online, that information is encrypted using a security protocol called SSL (Secure Sockets Layer), which encrypts all information prior to transmitting it over the Internet. We also use SSL to allow you to securely view your online account and registration information.
All credit/debit card details and personally identifiable information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third party
About Us
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
Blog
Here is our recent article on Online Shopping Tips featured on Middle East Living. Ann Rae, general manager of UAE-based online gift basket company, Mange Tout, offers top tips for the perfect gift purchase.
Read More...
Newsletter Sign Up
Get exclusive deals you will not find anywhere else straight to your inbox!
At Mange Tout you will find an outstanding selection of flowers, cakes and gift hampers to suit all occasions and people. Read More...
© 2017 Mange Tout Gifts Trading LLC. All Rights Reserved.Powered by SILICONEDGE.
You have no items in your shopping cart.
please wait...
